[The Tower of Whispers]
[برج الهمسات]
[Episode 5]
[الحلقة 5]
Get out of the way!
ابتعد عن الطريق!
Move!
يتحرك!
So fast!
سريع جداً!
Where are they rushing to?
إلى أين يتجهون؟
Such speed!
هذه السرعة!
Going so fast! Not afraid of hitting someone?
سريع جدًا! ألا تخاف من الاصطدام بأحد؟
How dangerous!
كم هو خطير!
Exactly!
بالضبط!
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Who's inside?
من بالداخل؟
-Take a look. -Isn't this Lord Ding?
-ألق نظرة. -أليس هذا اللورد دينغ؟
Who's that woman?
من تلك المرأة؟
Isn't that Lord Ding?
أليس هذا هو اللورد دينغ؟
Could she be a brothel girl?
هل يمكن أن تكون فتاة بيت دعارة؟
The girl is so old!
الفتاة كبيرة في السن!
Look at his face.
أنظر إلى وجهه.
All that lipstick marks!
كل تلك علامات أحمر الشفاه!
How embarrassing!
كم هو محرج!
Let's see how you'll survive in this city now.
دعونا نرى كيف ستتمكن من البقاء على قيد الحياة في هذه المدينة الآن.
Stop staring! Mind your own business!
توقف عن التحديق! اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة!
So this is what you wanted.
إذن هذا ما أردته.
Stop looking.
توقف عن النظر
Go away!
يبتعد!
So beautiful.
جميلة جداً.
♪ While the rain fades ♪
♪ بينما يتلاشى المطر ♪
You seem to have forgotten your place.
يبدو أنك نسيت مكانك.
♪ I wander once more through the old city upstream ♪
♪ أتجول مرة أخرى عبر المدينة القديمة أعلى النهر ♪
I mean
أعني
♪ Yet I cannot erase ♪
♪ ولكن لا يمكنني أن أمحو ♪
the flowers are so beautiful.
الزهور جميلة جداً.
♪ Mist-veiled tales that stir the river tides ♪
♪ حكايات غامضة تثير مد وجزر النهر ♪
♪ In fading dreams ♪
♪ في الأحلام الباهتة ♪
♪ Lanterns stain the worldly bustle with their glow ♪
♪ الفوانيس تلطخ صخب العالم بتوهجها ♪
♪ Today's tales sound off-key and hollow ♪
♪ حكايات اليوم تبدو غير متناغمة وجوفاء ♪
This Jun Che is quite obedient.
هذا جون تشي مطيع للغاية.
♪ Distorted, or left in fragments ♪
♪ مشوهة، أو متبقية في شظايا ♪
He didn't even try to dodge just now.
ولم يحاول حتى التهرب الآن.
♪ I heard the legends rise like the wind ♪
♪ سمعت الأساطير ترتفع مثل الريح ♪
Hya!
يا!
♪ Only to fall back into nothingness ♪
♪ فقط للسقوط مرة أخرى في العدم ♪
♪ I dare not disturb the toll of the bell ♪
♪ لا أجرؤ على إزعاج قرع الجرس ♪
♪ Nor dare I awaken the dream ♪
♪ ولا أجرؤ على إيقاظ الحلم ♪
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
♪ Fearing the retelling ♪
♪ خوفا من إعادة السرد ♪
♪ Could never capture that breathtaking glance back then ♪
♪ لم أستطع أبدًا التقاط تلك النظرة المذهلة في ذلك الوقت ♪
♪ Loving you was devotion beneath moon and breeze ♪
♪ حبك كان إخلاصًا تحت القمر والنسيم ♪
♪ Both ordinary love and hate ♪
♪ الحب والكراهية العاديين ♪
♪ Thus the era was shaken ♪
♪ وهكذا اهتز العصر ♪
♪ In youthful years of innocence ♪
♪ في سنوات الشباب من البراءة ♪
♪ When meetings would not come again ♪
♪ عندما لا تعود الاجتماعات مرة أخرى ♪
♪ The mortal realm was bound to start yet never end ♪
♪ كان من المفترض أن يبدأ عالم البشر ولكن لن ينتهي أبدًا ♪
I haven't completely taken down Ding Huairen yet.
لم أتمكن من القضاء على دينج هوايرين بشكل كامل بعد.
I'll go tie up the horse.
سأذهب لربط الحصان.
Since he's so obedient to me,
لأنه مطيع لي جدًا،
whether it's genuine or not,
سواء كان حقيقيا أم لا،
he's at least a good weapon.
إنه على الأقل سلاح جيد.
Five.
خمسة.
I'm coming in.
انا قادم.
Master?
يتقن؟
Why are you changing clothes with the door open?
لماذا تغير ملابسك والباب مفتوح؟
Put your clothes on quickly.
ارتدي ملابسك بسرعة.
Are you coming to bring me clothes, Master?
هل أنت قادم لتجلب لي الملابس يا سيدي؟
From today on,
من اليوم فصاعدا،
you will be my guard.
سوف تكون حارسي.
Here are your clothes.
ها هي ملابسك.
You don't need to call me Master anymore.
لا تحتاج إلى مناداتي بالسيد بعد الآن.
Just call me "My Lady".
فقط اتصل بي "سيدتي".
Thank you, My Lady.
شكرا لك سيدتي.
I'm leaving.
انا ذاهب.
From now on, wear these clean clothes.
من الآن فصاعدا، ارتدي هذه الملابس النظيفة.
My Lady.
سيدتي.
Since you bought me,
منذ أن اشتريتني،
I belong to you.
أنا أنتمي لك.
You can treat me as an object.
يمكنك أن تعاملني كشيء.
No need to mind the difference between men and women.
لا داعي للقلق بشأن الفرق بين الرجال والنساء.
Feel free to look.
لا تتردد في النظر.
Why am I nervous?
لماذا أنا متوترة؟
I just saw it the other day.
لقد رأيته للتو في اليوم الآخر.
I just took you into my home,
لقد أخذتك إلى منزلي للتو،
and the next moment you were indecent with Ding Huairen in the street?
وفي اللحظة التالية كنت غير لائق مع دينغ هوايرين في الشارع؟
Kneel!
اركع!
I didn't think it through.
لم أفكر في الأمر جيدا.
You know me.
أنت تعرفني.
I'm too naive, and I got fooled.
أنا ساذج جدًا، وقد خُدعت.
It's really not what you think.
إنه ليس حقا ما تعتقد.
Huirou.
هويرو.
Before our parents left,
قبل أن يغادر والدينا،
they asked you to take good care of me.
لقد طلبوا منك أن تعتني بي جيدًا.
This routine again.
هذا الروتين مرة أخرى.
Mother's getting soft-hearted again.
أصبحت الأم رقيقة القلب مرة أخرى.
How could you forget their words?
كيف يمكنك أن تنسى كلماتهم؟
How dare you mention our parents to me?
كيف تجرؤ على ذكر والديّ لي؟
If it weren't for our parents,
لو لم يكن لوالدينا،
would I have tolerated you until now?
هل كنت سأتحملك حتى الآن؟
I know you came to me in the capital
أعلم أنك أتيت إلي في العاصمة
not because you missed me.
ليس لأنك افتقدتني.
It's because you saw my husband rising in his career.
لأنك رأيت زوجي يرتفع في حياته المهنية.
You were envious and jealous,
لقد كنت حسودًا وغيورًا،
wanting a piece of our success.
نريد قطعة من نجاحنا.
But you should never,
ولكن لا ينبغي لك أبدا،
knowing Ding Huairen framed my husband,
مع العلم أن دينغ هوايرين هو من نصب الفخ لزوجي،
have had a secret affair with him.
لقد كانت لي علاقة سرية معه.
You want my whole family dead.
تريد موت عائلتي بأكملها.
How could you think of me like that?
كيف يمكنك أن تفكر بي بهذه الطريقة؟
I am your family.
انا عائلتك
It's precisely because we're family
هذا على وجه التحديد لأننا عائلة
that I've tolerated you
أنني تحملتك
and given you chance after chance.
وأعطاك فرصة بعد فرصة.
From now on, the doors of the Lu family
من الآن فصاعدا، أبواب عائلة لو
will be forever closed to you.
سوف يكون مغلقا أمامك إلى الأبد.
No!
لا!
Guards!
حراس!
-Yes.
-نعم.
Please forgive me, Huirou.
أرجوك أن تسامحني، هويرو.
Go!
يذهب!
Huirou, I was wrong.
هويرو، لقد كنت مخطئا.
Please forgive me.
رجائاً أعطني.
Huirou!
هويرو!
I'm your only sister.
أنا أختك الوحيدة.
[Lu's Mansion]
[قصر لو]
Are you really going to treat me like this?
هل حقا سوف تعاملني بهذه الطريقة؟
Huirou!
هويرو!
Let's enjoy our meal.
دعونا نستمتع بوجبتنا.
Good girl.
فتاة جيدة.
Try this.
جرب هذا.
Today, with Ding Huairen's scandal exposed,
اليوم، مع الكشف عن فضيحة دينغ هوايرين ،
he has only himself to blame.
ليس عليه أن يلوم إلا نفسه.
He is Consort Yun's brother.
إنه شقيق الزوجة يون.
He's been using that connection
لقد كان يستخدم هذا الاتصال
to secretly secure control over
لتأمين السيطرة سرا على
the Eldest Prince's investiture ceremony.
حفل تنصيب الأمير الأكبر.
[Act with Integrity]
[التصرف بنزاهة]
He's been secretly
لقد كان سرا
competing with me for quite some time.
تتنافس معي لبعض الوقت.
Now that this scandal has broken out,
والآن بعد أن اندلعت هذه الفضيحة،
will it affect the investiture ceremony?
هل سيؤثر ذلك على حفل التنصيب؟
Of course it will.
بالطبع سوف يحدث ذلك.
Now his secret maneuvering
الآن مناوراته السرية
has been exposed.
لقد تم الكشف عنها.
I heard
لقد سمعت
he's about to be demoted and sent to the border.
إنه على وشك أن يتم تخفيض رتبته وإرساله إلى الحدود.
So the investiture ceremony
لذا فإن حفل التنصيب
will now be your responsibility, Father?
هل ستكون مسئوليتك الآن يا أبي؟
Naturally.
بطبيعة الحال.
This is truly worth celebrating.
وهذا يستحق الاحتفال حقا.
We should indeed celebrate.
ينبغي لنا أن نحتفل بالفعل.
Yes.
نعم.
Cai Ping.
كاي بينغ.
Quickly bring us some warm wine.
أحضر لنا بسرعة بعض النبيذ الدافئ.
Yes, Master.
نعم سيدي.
Everything is moving in a good direction again.
كل شيء يتحرك في الاتجاه الجيد مرة أخرى.
Here, Yingying,
هنا، ينغ يينغ،
I can finally breathe a sigh of relief now, can't I?
أستطيع أخيرا أن أتنفس الصعداء الآن، أليس كذلك؟
This is the lead our scouts found.
هذا هو الدليل الذي وجده كشافونا.
There's a girl called Li
هناك فتاة اسمها لي
who might be a spy from the Yue State.
من قد يكون جاسوسًا من ولاية يوي؟
Where is she hiding now?
أين تختبئ الآن؟
Fengman House.
بيت فينجمان.
Fengman House?
منزل فينجمان؟
Take care, Sir.
اعتني بنفسك يا سيدي.
My Lord, please come in.
سيدي، من فضلك ادخل.
Take care.
يعتني.
Let go!
اتركه!
We're here to investigate.
نحن هنا للتحقيق.
I don't recognize this official.
لا أعرف هذا المسؤول.
Do you have a preferred girl?
هل لديك فتاة مفضلة؟
Which room is Miss Li in?
في أي غرفة تتواجد الآنسة لي؟
Miss Li isn't receiving guests today.
السيدة لي لا تستقبل الضيوف اليوم.
Miss Cui is just as good.
السيدة كوي جيدة أيضًا.
Cui!
أيّ!
-Coming. -Check the first floor and the lobby.
-قادم. -تحقق من الطابق الأول والردهة.
[Fengman House]
[بيت فنغمان]
Yes.
نعم.
I'll search upstairs.
سأبحث في الطابق العلوي.
Move aside.
تنحى جانبا.
My Lord.
سيدي.
-This...
-هذا...
Coming, My Lord!
قادم يا سيدي!
Step aside. Official investigation.
تنحى جانباً. تحقيق رسمي.
Young Master, do you have a favorite girl?
سيدي الشاب، هل لديك فتاة مفضلة؟
Official investigation.
تحقيق رسمي.
Miss.
يفتقد.
What's wrong with you?
ما مشكلتك؟
My Lord,
سيدي
save me.
أنقذني.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
We, the Longxiang Guards, are here to investigate a case.
نحن، حراس لونغشيانغ، هنا للتحقيق في قضية.
How dare you toy with me like this!
كيف تجرؤ على اللعب معي بهذه الطريقة!
There's no case to investigate here.
لا توجد قضية للتحقيق هنا.
Now that you've entered this cage,
الآن بعد أن دخلت هذا القفص،
why don't you investigate me instead?
لماذا لا تقوم بالتحقيق معي بدلا من ذلك؟
My Lord, do you also like
يا سيدي هل تحب أيضا
the scent of my cosmetics, My Lord?
رائحة مستحضرات التجميل الخاصة بي يا سيدي؟